[('Clients', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Stanford', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('STC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Interest', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Consolidation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('USA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('FASB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('BDO', 'LOCATION'), (')', 'PERSON'), ('WCL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('BlackRock', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('EDGAR', 'PERSON'), ('SGC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lending', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Variable', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Deloitte', 'PERSON'), ('BDO', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('LLC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Holdings', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Enron', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('California', 'LOCATION'), ('Accounting', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('BDO', 'PERSON'), ('Quick', 'LOCATION'), ('PCAOB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Inc.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Southern', 'LOCATION'), ('Robert', 'PERSON'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UCC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Transfers', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION'), ('Financial', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Assets', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Group', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Herz', 'PERSON'), ('BOFI', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Entities', 'ORGANIZATION'), (',', 'ORGANIZATION')]